字幕转制｜天外生物
感谢原字幕制作者
快 快点！
Come, come, come on. Hit it!
看！他拐到三号路了！
Watch it! He cuttin' through third!
麻烦！
Trouble!
- 我对付司机  - 闭嘴吧！快！打开车门！
- I got the driver.  - Shut your ass! Get to runnin'! Open the door!
你小子 下车！下车！
Get your dumb ass out the car! Get your ass out!
下车！到后面去！
Get your ass out the car! Get your ass to the back!
我叫你到后面去！
I said get to the back!
打开后门
Open that motherfucker up.
把包包拿出来！
Get the bag out!
快！拿出来！
Come on! Let's go! Let's get out!
混蛋！
Motherfucker!
这是怎么一回事？
What the fuck is this?
- 该死！ - 唐斯！
- Fuck!  - Downs!
当心！
Watch out!
卡斯！
Cass!
- 我没子弹了！ - 低身！
- I'm out!  - Stay down!
该死！
Shit!
该死 我们怎么办？
Shit. What do we do?
别管包包了 我们走吧 快
Forget about the bag. Let's get out of here. Come on, man.
上车 我们走
Get in. Let's go.
我们走 快 快点！
Let's move. Let's go. Come on!
我们走 我们走！快！
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go! Come on!
该死的！
Damn it!
怎么一回事？
What the fuck was that?
- 刚才怎么一回事？ - 不确定
- Shit. What the fuck was that?  - Not sure.
几公斤货 这么多人
Fucking couple guys, couple kilos.
没错 都是全付武装的
No, man. That was reservoir dog shit back there.
没想到 他们这么大动干戈
I didn't know they was gonna come in hot like that.
有多少货？包很重
How much is in there? That bag is heavy.
据我目测 至少有二十五公斤
Shit. Just from my eyes, got to be 25 or better in here, man.
- 不可能这么多  - 一定是二十五公斤以上
- Oh, god, there ain't no 25.  - Yeah. Got to be 25 or more.
我虽然没带计算器
Man, listen. I ain't got my calculator with me,
但这些货 在市面上 能卖七八百万美元
but they got to be seven or eight million on the streets.
能让你做个整形手术了
Enough for plastic surgery, fix your face.
- 我的脸很好看 干嘛整形？ - 当然要
- My face is beautiful. Why change that?  - What you mean?
- 你面具掉了 他们看到了你的脸  - 无所谓
- Your mask came off. They saw you, nigga.  - It don't matter.
- 我喜欢我的脸 这是艺术品  - 随你怎么说
- I like my face. It's a work of art.  - Whatever you say.
这可是你的命
It's your life, bro.
不眠夜
是我 我要上连班
It's me. I got called for a double.
所以 你要送托马斯去比赛
So you got to take Thomas to his game.
三点半 来医院接他
Just come get himfrom the hospital at 3:30
文森特 这次别再失信了
and, vin,don't fuck it up again.
再见
Bye.
索伦森医生
Dr. Sorenson.
- 叫我露比  - 露比
- Ruby.  - Ruby.
你今早没来
You missed our appointment this morning.
不跟你谈谈 我不能准许你回来工作
I cannot approve your return to the workplace until we talk.
警局的人 很担心你最近的行为
Guys at the department are concerned about your recent behavior.
警局的人？
The guys at the department?
全警局的人 都在说我的闲话
The whole damn department is gossiping about me.
那么
Well,
你对此 是什么感觉？
how does that make you feel?
我是什么感觉？感觉很好
How's that make me feel? Fucking fantastic.
你还是告诉我 发生了什么吧
Why don't you tell me what happened
用你自己的话
in your own words?
好吧
Okay.
说出来 否则我就留着它
Say it out loud, or I'm gonna keep this.
我本以为 当时情况 在控制之下
Thought I was walking into a controlled situation.
结果却进了一个毒品工厂 碰到一个愤怒的瘾君子
Instead, I found myself in the middle of a meth lab with a pissed-off junkie.
- 他打你了？ - 打得不轻
- He assaulted you?  - He kicked my ass.
- 好吗？ - 好
- Okay?  - Okay.
毒品工厂 并不隐秘
Meth labs aren't quiet. Meth labs stink.
有人知道这工厂的存在 还有的人 收了贿赂 不去调查
Someone knew the lab was there, and someone was paid to look the other way.
我知道了
I hear you.
好的 那你知道 我必须回去工作
Good. Good. So you know i have to get back to work.
我必须查清此事
I have to figure this thing out.
因为这城市 有太多的腐败警察
'Cause this city is crawling with dirty cops.
你听说了吗？
Do you hear that?
我是布莱思特
Bryant.
好
Okay.
我的搭档 打来电话
So this is my partner on the other line.
在一个犯罪现场 发现了警用子弹
They found government-issued bullets at a crime scene.
是要我继续调查 还是听你继续胡扯？
So can I go do my job, or do you want to keep talking bullshit?
我这就去
I'm on my way.
谢谢 我现在感觉好多 了
Thank you. I feel so much better now.
珍妮弗
Jennifer.
早安 警尉
Morning, lieutenant.
凌晨四点二十七分 一辆警车 接到枪击案报案
So at 0427, a squad car got a shots fired call
与此同时 我们还接到报案
about the same time we got a report
在老城区 有一辆新型轿车超速
about a late-model sedan speeding near old downtown.
那警车去了枪击案现场
The unit checking out the shots fired
在三号路旁的一条小巷里 发现了两具尸体
went into an alley off of third street where they found two dead bodies.
他们报告说 现场有很多蛋壳
These responding officers report casings everywhere.
- 大量的  - 我们侦查此案
- And I mean everywhere.  - Oh, we'll take that.
我和卡斯
Me and cass.
不 我要交给艾莫森和弗兰尼根
No. I'm giving it to Emerson and flannigan.
你是想交给他们 还是想破案？
You want cagney and Lacey to take it or you wanna get it solved?
好吧 交给你们调查
All right, hotshot. It's yours.
好
Yeah.
走吧 搭档
Let's go, partner.
你疯了吗？你这是干什么？
Hey, say, nigga, is you high? What the fuck are you doing?
是有一点 我们要控制这个案子
Yeah, a little bit. We got to control this case.
控制了这个案子 就控制了证据
We control the case, we control the evidence.
这可能是你做过的 最明智或着最傻的事
That might be smartest shit or the dumbest shit you ever did.
有可能 最傻的事 是今早的事
It might be. The dumbest shit was this morning.
在找这个吗？
Looking for this?
我什么都找
I'm looking for everything.
这是警用子弹 不止这些
Mm. It's police-issued, and there's more of 'em.
看来 是同一把枪 杀了那个大汉
Looks like the same gun killed the big guy.
我是重案组的文森特唐斯
Vincent downs, homicide.
珍妮弗布莱思特
Jennifer Bryant.
那是我的搭档 道格丹尼森
That's my partner, Doug dennison.
我们是内务司的
We're internal affairs.
好 你只知道这些？警用子弹？
Okay. So that's all you got, huh? Government-issue?
此人身上 有拉克萨斯赌场的工作证
This one's got an employee ID from the luxus casino.
而那个大汉不一样
The big guy? He's a special snowflake.
十二年前 就有被捕记录
Arrest records going back 12 years.
- 你的脸 怎么了？ - 你何不靠近看看？
- What happened to your face?  - Why don't you take a closer look?
只是 人人都在谈论你的情况
It's just everybody's been talking about your situation.
热门话题
Talk of the town.
- 你的脸 怎么了？ - 没怎么
- What happened to your face?  - Nothing happened.
这是一张专注于细节的脸
This is a face that pays attention to details.
说到细节 这案子 不是艾莫森和弗兰尼根负责的吗
Speaking of details, i thought Emerson and flannigan were assigned to this case.
不 你听错了 布莱恩特
No, no. Maybe you shouldn't think, Bryant.
- 交给我和我的搭档了  - 是吗
- Me and my partner got the call.  - You did?
我是为了保护一位警察同事受的伤
Anyway, I was just looking out for a fellow officer. Mm.
你该冰敷一下
You should put some ice on that. Yeah.
好 我也会给你拿些冰
Yeah. I'll get some for you too.
女士们 先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
内华达州的警察
Nevada's finest.
我感觉 需要洗个澡
I feel like i need a shower.
- 那人说什么了？ - 他对我撒谎
- What'd that guy want?  - He lied to me
当我问他 为何是他调查此案
when I asked why he was on the case.
拉斯韦加斯警方 阻碍内务司调查
Vegas pd fucking with an ia investigation.
- 此人不好对付  - 我喜欢
- Got a bulldog.  - Yeah. Love it.
我们该查查他 神探
We should look into that, Sherlock.
临床护理专家 请去六一三病房
Clinicalnurse specialist, 613.
临床护理专家 请马上去六一三病房
Available clinicalnurse specialist,stat, 613, please.
血气专家 马上去心脏病监护室
Blood gas tech to ccu, stat.
- 血气专家 马上去心脏病监护室  - 嗨
- Blood gas tech to ccu, stat.  - Hey.
嗨
Hey.
我说了三点半 他四点之前要到
I said 3:30. He's got to be there by 4:00.
对不起 我给你买了花 所以 来晚了
Sorry. I was grabbing you some flowers. That's why I was running late.
谢谢
Thank you.
这是什么？
What's that?
- 我本想告诉你的 但你一直不来  - 这是什么？
- I was gonna tell you, but you kept canceling.  - What is this?
- 这是什么戒指？ - 订婚戒指
- What kind of ring is this?  - It's an engagement ring.
- 是戴维送的？ - 当然是戴维
- It's from Dave?  - Yeah, it's Dave. Who else...
你这是干什么？
what are you doing? What am i...
你想跟他过一辈子吗？
is this who you want to spend the rest of your life with?
- 你考虑清楚了吗？ - 是的 戴维能经常来
- Have you thought this out?  - Yeah. Dave shows up.
- 戴维照顾你儿子  - 我不管他来多少趟
- Dave takes care of your son.  - I don't care how many times he shows up.
- 他不是他爸爸 我是他爸爸  - 我知道你是
- He ain't his father. I'm his father.  - I know you are.
你要尊重这一点 德娜
You gotta respect that, d. Yeah.
我该怎么办？
So what am I supposed to do?
- 难道他就…  - 他就照顾你的家人？
- He's just supposed to...  - just supposed to come in and take care of your family?
- 是吗？ - 好吧 德娜
- That?  - Okay, d.
好吧 好吧
All right. All right.
他必须走了 他的比赛要开始了
Look, he's got to go. His game is now.
你要去接他 因为我还有事
You got to pick him up, 'cause I got stuff I got to do...no, no.
别再来了 别再来了
Not again. Not again. Not again.
我要上连班 你自己想办法
I have to work a double. You figure it out.
好 孩子 跟爸爸一起玩吧
All right, baby, enjoy your dad.
九点把他送回去 好吗？
Drop him off by 9:00 pm. Okay?
把花还给我
Give me my flowers back.
九点 再见 孩子
9:00 pm. Bye, baby.
再见
Bye.
儿子
Hey, son.
要花吗？
Want some flowers?
你怎么没告诉我戴维的事
How come you didn't tell me about Dave, hmm?
你怎么没告诉他经常来
How come you ain't tell me he coming around more?
你应该告诉我的 坦率地告诉我
You should have told me. Supposed to be man-to-man on that.
- 应该让我知道  - 你为何关心？
- You supposed to let me know what's going on.  - Why the hell you care?
因为 关心是我的职责
Because it's my business to care.
他下周就搬来
He's moving in next week. No, no.
不 这不会的 不会的
No, ain't nobody doing that. Not doing that. Not doing that.
你需要地方住 就来我家 我有的是地方
You need a place to stay, stay with me. I got plenty of room.
- 你有地方  - 是的 我有地方
- You got room.  - Yeah, I got room.
难道我是一件家具吗？
What am I, a piece of furniture?
你不关心我住在哪里 和谁住一起
You don't care where I live, who I live with.
我们一家三口 住在一起的时侯 你很少在家
You were never home when mom and I lived with you!
要知道
You see now...
我爱你妈妈 我爱你
I love your mom. I love you.
这不过有些事… 我不好解释的事
It's just, I mean, things that...that I can't explain.
很复杂
It just gets complicated.
收音机坏了
Radio don't work.
拿出来吧
Take it out.
还记得 我教你怎么用枪吗
Remember what I told you to do with that.
扣扳机之前要想好了 开弓没有回头箭
You pull that trigger, you better have your mind made up. You can't take it back.
不管你瞄准的是什么…
And whatever you aiming at...
要确定 自己真想杀它
Make sure you prepared to kill it.
喂
Yeah?
唐斯先生 我是斯坦鲁比诺
Mr. downs, this is Stan rubino.
听说 你手上有我的东西
I learned you have something that's mine.
你抢走的二十五公斤可卡因
The 25 kilos of cocaine you stole.
听着 那是我错了 我会把货给你
Listen, that was a mistake. I'll get you your product.
如果你伤害他… 你知道 是什么后果
Look, if you hurt him... You know what it is.
唐斯先生 别激动
Mr. downs, let's not get carried away.
你知道 我是什么人
I guess you know what kind of man I am.
好 我把货给你 我亲自送过去
Okay. Okay. I'll get your stuff and I'll bring it right to you.
三小时后 罗伯特诺瓦克 要来拿二十五公斤
In three hours, rob novak's coming to pick up 25 kilos.
如果我给不出货
If I can't deliver,
- 我会把你儿子给他  - 求你了
- I'll give him your son instead.  - Please.
他才十六岁
He's only 16.
他十六岁
He's 16.
是的 我知道
Yes, I know.
谢丽 你妈还好吗
Sheri, how's your mom?
她好些了 谢谢你送的花
She's better. Thank you for the flowers.
这是我们应该做的
Ah, it's the least we could do.
我是布莱思特 我需要 一位警官的资料 文森特唐斯
Hey, this is Bryant. I need a file on an officer...Vincent downs.
联系人信息 车牌号码 家人信息
Contact information, license plate, family info.
不需要批准的话 你能告诉我多少
What can you give me without approval?
谢谢
Thank you.
啊
Aaah. Whew.
Aaah.
你是怎么了？
What's up with you?
你没事吧？这些血 哪里来的？
You all right? Man, where all this blood come from?
你搞砸了 卡斯
You messed up, cass.
你什么意思
What you mean?
斯坦鲁比诺 抓走了托马斯
Stan rubino got Thomas.
斯坦鲁比诺 抓走了托马斯？
Stan rubino got Thomas?
- 拉克萨斯赌场的经理？ - 是的
- The manager from the luxus?  - The manager from luxus.
- 你搞砸了  - 你什么意思
- You fucked up.  - What the fuck...
我们抢的 不是鲁比诺的货 是诺瓦克的货
we weren't stealing from rubino. You were stealing from novak.
你让我们招惹了诺瓦克
You got us fucked up in novak shit!
- 我并不知道…  - 你怎么会不知道
- I didn't know...  - how you not know?
他们说 这票很轻松
They said it was gonna be an easy grab.
并不轻松 他们抓走了托马斯！
It ain't no easy grab! They got t!
我们得…他们会杀了…
Man, we gotta...man, they gonna kill...they gonna...
我知道 我需要那个包包！
I know what they doin'! I need that bag!
你知道 我不是故意的
You know I wouldn't do that shit on purpose!
- 那你为何干？ - 我原本不知道？
- Then why'd you do it?  - Hey, man, I didn't know!
- 我对托马斯 视同己出  - 你只和他相处了一天！
- Man, I love Thomas like he my own!  - Had one day with him!
听着 我理解你生气
Hey, listen. I understand you upset.
我会解决的 你冷静
Man, I'll fix it. Calm down.
把包包拿来
Get the bag.
你竟然以为 我会干出这种事
I can't believe you thought I'd do some shit like that, man.
我回去的时候 会联系你
I hit you when I'm on the way back.
天啊
Oh, god.
罗伯特
Rob.
你不必这么做
You don't have to do this.
我们是一家人
We're family, man.
你不能这么对待家人？求你了
You don't do this to family, okay? Please!
求你了 我很抱歉 好吗？
Please. Please. Okay. I am sorry, okay?
我非常非常抱歉
I am so, so sorry.
你不要…拜托
You don't...please.
请别这么做 请别这么做！
Please don't do this. Please don't do this!
啊！
Aaah!
我的一位朋友 给了我一份通话记录
Friend of mine gave me some cell phone records.
三天前 两个电话
Three weeks ago, two calls.
周四是五个电话 昨天又有四个电话
And five calls Thursday and four more yesterday
你的手机 打给缉毒局的
from your phone to the DEA.
- 不是我打的  - 听着 混蛋
- Th-that wasn't me.  - Listen, you dumb motherfucker.
你以为 我们没有收买人
You think that we don't have people who we pay to tell us
告诉我们 有亲戚给缉毒局打电话了吗？
when our relatives call the fucking DEA?
对不起 我结交了阿瓜普列塔的一个女子
I'm sorry. Uh, I was with this girl in agua prieta, all right?
缉毒局逮捕了我们 问了我们很多问题
And-and the DEA, they busted us, and they asked me all these questions.
知道我父亲 怎么评价你们这一支吗？
You know what my father always said about your side of the family?
你们都是重色轻友之人
You only think with your dick.
不是因为这个女人 就是那个女人
It's always this fat girl and that fat girl.
所以 你才这么傻
And that's why you turned out so stupid.
因为 你爸娶了你妈
'Cause your daddy married your mom and fucked her.
漂亮的女子 但不是那种应该娶回家的人
Sweet lady. But not the kind of face you want to look at for the rest of your life.
缉毒局查抄
DEA bust.
我的毒品工厂 上周被查抄了
My cut house raided last week.
凭我的身份
The position I'm in,
还要去求斯坦鲁比诺这样的混蛋
I got to go begging a fuck-nut scumbag
给我二十五公斤货
like Stanley rubino for 25 kilos.
这很没面子
It's embarrassing.
更糟的是
Even worse,
整个世界 都知道了我的软弱
the whole goddamn world knows I'm vulnerable.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我知道 你抱歉
Yeah, I know you are.
割掉他的舌头
Cut off his tongue.
让他再也说不了话
Make sure he doesn't ever use it again.
不 不 罗伯特 回来！
No, no. Rob! Rob, come back!
别这么做 拜托 拜托 别这么做
You can't do...please! Please! Please, don't do...
别这么对我！
please don't do this to me!
不 不 拜托
No, no, no, no, no, no. N-n-no, please...
快 让我出去！
Come on. Let me out!
有人吗？
Anyone!
救命
Help!
该死的！
Shit!
该死
Shit.
- 嗨 德娜  - 托马斯在哪里 文森特？
- Hey, d.  - Where's Thomas, vin?
没事的
It's okay.
他的教练打了电话 说他没去比赛 他在哪里？
His coach called, said he missed the game. Where is he?
他走了不久
Yeah, yeah. He took off a little while ago.
我大概知道他在哪里 我就去接他
I think I know where he is. I'm gonna get him now.
走了？他从不错过比赛
Took off? He'd never miss a game.
德娜 我和托马斯发生了争吵
Look, d, t and i had a little fight.
他现在可能只是故意气我
So, uh, I think he's just punishing me right now.
- 什么样的争吵 文森特  - 不知道
- What kind of fight, vin?  - I don't know.
他就那个脾气
He was just being him.
- 我也知道 你那个脾气  - 是啊
- And I'm sure you were just being you.  - Yeah.
总之 我不同意他干某件事
Look, at the end of the day, I told him no, he couldn't do something,
他就生气走了 我大概知道 他在哪里
he got pissed off, he took off, so I think I know where he is.
- 我就去接他  - 找到他
- I'm gonna go get him right now.  - Find him.
一楼
First floor.
那里
There.
他在干什么？
What the hell's he doing?
一楼
First floor.
是诺瓦克
It's novak.
嗨 罗伯特
Hey, rob.
是的 终于一切妥当了
Yeah, and we're finally all set here. Right.
在一楼见面 再见
Meet you on the floor. Bye.
跟我来
Follow me.
我是警察 这里几分钟前 来了一个人
Police. There was a man in here a few minutes ago.
- 他提了个帆布包  - 我没注意到
- He had a duffel bag.  - I didn't notice.
是个大帆布包
It was a big duffel bag.
我说了 我没注意到
And I'm telling you i didn't notice.
你要干什么？
What are you doing?
这是男厕所
This is the men's room.
好吧 好吧
Okay. Okay.
好吧
Okay.
来过一个人 像你这么折腾
There was a guy banging around just like you in that one.
你应该说 你找的是黑人 六英尺高
You should have said he was black, six-feet-tall,
在厕所里折腾
banging around in the stalls.
- 那我就知道 你说的是谁了  - 谢谢
- Then I would have known who you were talking about.  - Thanks.
我会描述的更清楚一些
I'll work on my descriptions.
哦
Oh.
这混蛋
Motherfucker.
我就知道
I knew it.
你的毒品呢？
Where are my drugs?
我儿子呢？
Where's my son?
爸爸！
Dad!
托马斯
Thomas.
这是怎么回事？
What's goin' on?
不会有事的
It's gonna be okay.
拜托
Come on, man.
你抢了我的货
You steal from me...
还杀了我的人
And you kill my guys.
我们好商量
Let's just figure it out.
你这蠢货
You stupid shit.
这是我运过的 最大的一批货
This is the biggest amount I ever moved.
难道我会不严加保护吗？
You think i wouldn't protect it with everything I've got?
我们不知道 毒品是你的
Look, we didn't know the drugs was yours.
你不知道 你闯出了什么祸
You have no idea what kind of mess you've made here.
那可卡因 本来是送到诺瓦克那里的
That cocaine is supposed to go to the novaks.
你知道 他们的能耐
You know what they're capable of.
这件事 我该怎么跟罗伯特诺瓦克解释
How am I supposed to explain this to rob novak?
或是他父亲？
Or his father?
如果弗兰克亲自过问…
If frank gets involved here...
我把毒品给你带来了
I got your drugs.
其他的 我藏起来了
I got the rest stashed.
把儿子给我 我就去把它拿来
I'll get it to you when I get my son.
真不明白你 唐斯
I don't get you, downs.
做事有正确的方式 有错误的方式
There's a right way to do things and a wrong way.
你就是不肯按规矩来
I just don't think that you respect the established protocol.
是的
Yeah.
我一般都是用正确的方式做事
The right way is how i usually do things.
十分钟
Ten minutes.
十分钟后 我会带来 来接我儿子
I'll bring it back in ten minutes, get my son.
- 带我去哪里 爸爸  - 十分钟
- No, where am I going? Dad!  - Ten minutes.
如何保证 我把可卡因拿来 你就会把儿子给我？
How do I know if I bring you that coke, you don't give my son back?
我们走吧？
Shall we?
喂？
Hello?
我跟踪文森特唐斯 到了拉克萨斯赌场
I followed Vincent downs to the luxus.
干嘛跟踪他？
What do you mean you followed Vincent downs?
我们谈过 你说该调查一下他
We discussed it. You said he was worth looking into.
调查并不等于跟踪 南希朱尔
Yeah, looking into does not mean tailing, Nancy drew.
他在男厕所天花板内 藏了二十三公斤可卡因
He hid 23 kilos of coke in the ceiling of the men's bathroom.
所以 我说他 值得调查一下
So I'm saying he's worth looking in to.
好 封锁厕所 我马上就去
Okay, seal off the bathroom. I'm on my way.
- 我把它拿出厕所了  - 你没做调查
- I took it out of the bathroom.  - You moved evidence
就把证物拿走了？
without properly conducting an investigation?
拿走证物 是因为需要拿走
I moved evidence because it needed to be moved.
我在前门等你
I'm waiting out front for you.
呵呵
Oh, ho, ho.
你会收到一堆警戒线 做为生日礼物的
Oh, you are getting a roll of police tape for your birthday.
给你
Here you go.
去拿货 在我办公室等我 五分钟
Get the stuff now. Meet me in my office. Five minutes.
- 罗伯特  - 斯坦
- Rob.  - Stanley.
很高兴见到你
Good to see you.
- 你父亲还好吗？ - 他很好
- Oh, hey, how's the old man?  - He's good.
十…
Ten...
又来了
here we go again.
不管你在找什么 一个女警察 已经进去过了
Whatever you're looking for, that lady cop was already in there.
该死的！
Shit!
她怎么进去了？
What do you mean she was already in there? Huh?
她有没有拿着垃圾袋？
She have a garbage bag?
你没听见吗？
You don't hear me?
没有？
No, huh?
她有没有…
Did she have a gar...
好 听着 听着
all right, listen. Listen.
听着 我需要找回那个垃圾袋
Listen. I need to get that garbage bag.
这个给你
You take this.
这是我父亲的表
It's my father's watch.
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
拜托
Please.
我们喝一杯吧
Let's get a drink.
不了 我还赶时间
No. No. I'm in a bit of a hurry.
只想拿着我的货 走人
I just want to get my stuff and go.
我的人 正把货拿到我的办公室 只需要再过几分钟
My guy's bringing the stuff to my office. Just be a few more minutes.
出什么事了吗？
Something wrong?
没有 一切正常
No. Everything's fine.
我有一瓶上好的 二十五年陈酿麦卡伦威士忌
I got a great 25-year-old bottle of macallan up there
上面贴着你的名字
with your name on it.
你意下如何？
What do you say?
你知道 我不喝酒
Now, you know i don't drink.
- 不过 喝一杯也无妨  - 去你办公室吧
- But sure.  - Let's go to your office.
嘿
Hey.
这是你的
This is yours.
谢谢
Thanks.
好
Yeah.
斯坦
Stanley,
还要多久？
how much longer?
几分钟
A few minutes.
几分钟？
A few minutes?
是这样的
Here's the thing.
你知道 我的家族
You know my family.
我们涉足很多行业
And we got our fingers in a whole lot of pies.
毕竟
I mean, shit,
谁不想分一杯羹呢？
who doesn't love a hot, steaming slice of pie?
美味
Delicious.
但我父亲 考虑深远
But my father, he's a...he's a big thinker.
我们正开发一个新市场
We got a new pie getting baked up.
加拿大
Canada.
没办法？他喜欢雪
What can I say? He likes snow.
听我说 罗伯特
Listen, rob...
不 斯坦 好听的在后面
no, Stanley, it gets better.
这本来是一件小事
It was supposed to be a small deal this week...
二十五公斤可卡因 只是先给他们尝尝
25 kilos, you know, just to give them a taste.
但我的蠢货表弟 成了缉毒局的线人
Then my idiot cousin decides to become a DEA informant,
我们失去了整整…
and we lose an entire...
一批货
Shipment.
但我站了出来
But me, I step up
向我父亲保证 加拿大的市场 不会有问题
and I promise my father that our Canadian pie is safe,
我可以弥补这损失
and that I could cover the shortage
再搞来…
with an extra...
二十五公斤
25 kilos.
你的二十五公斤
Your 25 kilos.
- 我只是帮忙  - 不 斯坦利
- I was just trying to help.  - No, Stanley.
你提出给我一批货 那是帮我
When you made me the offer, you were helping me out.
但当我向父亲保证 不会有问题之后
But when I promised my father that I had it all covered,
这就成了你的责任
then you became obligated.
那我
So,
我的可卡因在哪里？
where is my goddamn cocaine?
好的
Okay.
你能等一下吗？谢谢
Can you hold one moment, please? Thank you.
我想租一个储物柜？
I'd like to rent a locker, please?
对不起 储物柜 只能温泉的客人使用
I'm sorry. Lockers are reserved for spa guests only.
如果你想预订…
If you'd like to book a...
我想租一个储物柜
I'd like to rent a locker, please.
谢谢
Thank you.
一楼
First floor.
- 你查过所有摄影机了吗？ - 是的 没找到他
- Did you check every monitor?  - Yes. I lost him.
- 该死的  - 他儿子在我们手上
- Goddamn it.  - We got his kid.
他会把毒品给我们的 斯坦
He's gonna bring us our drugs. Stan...
嘿 你不是说 在外面等我的吗
hey, I thought you said you'd meet me outside.
- 我就知道他腐败  - 他在哪里？
- I knew he was dirty.  - Where is he?
我只顾保护证物了
I stayed with the evidence.
我的天
Jesus Christ.
首先 有一名死者 是这里的员工
First of all, we got a dead guy who worked here.
我跟踪斯坦来这里
Right? I followed downs here
看到他跟赌场经理 斯坦罗比诺交谈
and see him talking to the casino manager, Stan rubino.
然后罗伯特诺瓦克带着人来了 跟罗比诺见了面
Then rob novak and his guys turn up, and they're meeting with rubino.
这显然 跟今早的犯罪现场有关
Clearly, this ties in to our crime scene this morning.
为什么 就因为我们在犯罪现场 发现了警用子弹？
Why? Because we've got a police-issued bullet at the crime scene,
还因为 唐斯来了这里
and because downs comes here
把一批可卡因 藏在厕所天花板内？
and shoves a ton of cocaine into the bathroom ceiling?
那么 就是他杀的人
Then he killed the guy.
是的
Yes.
好 他是嫌疑人了
Okay, he's our guy.
你把毒品 放哪里了
Where'd you put the drugs?
放在温泉 一个储物柜里了
I put them in a locker in the spa.
天啊 这是胡闹 这是胡闹
Oh, my god. This is nuts. This is nuts.
- 我们要找个法官批准  - 不
- We got to get a judge in on this.  - No.
如果我们等待批准 就会错过了 这是大事
If we hang around waiting for paperwork, we'll miss it. This is big.
如果我们同时查获了 诺瓦克家族和一个腐败警察
We can bring down the novaks and have an internal bust at the same time?
- 珍妮弗  - 我是对的
- Jennifer...  - I'm right about this.
- 珍妮弗  - 我没事
- Jen...  - I'm fine.
好 你想做什么？
Okay. What do you want to do?
我想试探一下唐斯
I want to give downs a poke.
该死
Shit.
嗨 德娜
Hey, d.
- 你找到他了吗  - 是的 收到他的一个短信
- Do you have him?  - Yeah. Got a text from him.
- 他说要去拉克萨斯赌场 见个女孩  - 什么女孩？
- Said he was going to meet some shorty at the luxus casino.  - What girl?
你知道的 经常和他在一起的那个女孩
You know, the...with the girl. The girl, uh...the girl he always with.
- 那个…  - 他没女朋友
- The girl...  - he doesn't have a girl.
也许他不希望你知道
Maybe he don't want you to know who the girl is.
我了解你 文森特 了解你的声音
I know you, vin, and I know your voice.
你没对我说实话吧？
You're not telling me the whole story, are you?
现在别扯这些 我找到他后 会给你打电话的 好吗？
Don't start that right now. When I get him, i will call you, okay?
我找到他后 给你打电话
I'll call you when I got him. Shit.
文森特
Look, vin...
嗨 唐斯
Hey, downs.
你知道 机场的庸播
You know what they say at the airport.
要照顾好自己的行李
Never leave your bag unattended.
布莱思特 我需要那个包包
Bryant, I need that bag.
- 我们见个面谈谈吧？ - 去你的吧！
- Why don't we meet up and talk about it?  - Fuck you!
好
Okay.
我必须离开这里
Oh, I gotta get out of here.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
鲁比诺先生 叫人把一瓶cristal
Mr. rubino has requested a bottle of cristal
马上送到他的办公室
sent to his office, immediately.
- 记在他的账上  - 好
- Put it on his personal account.  - Okay.
送到他办公室 好吗？
To his office, okay?
很高兴 你终于来了
Nice of you to finally join us.
怎么这么久才来？
What the hell took you so long?
这个人是谁？
Who the fuck is this?
他是文森特唐斯 他拿来了你的货
This is Vincent downs. He's the man who's got your product.
为什么等了你这么长时间？
And why have we been sitting around waiting on you?
栖下有很多警察
There's a lot of cops downstairs.
赌场里 来了很多警察 我们必须走
Cops all over the casino. We need to get out of here.
赌场里 总是有很多警察
Casino's always full of cops.
- 他们跟踪你了？ - 是的
- They follow you?  - Think so.
是缉毒局的 他们知道 我们在这里
And, uh, it's narcotics. They know we're up here.
你怎么知道 他们是缉毒局的？
How do you know they're narcotics?
因为我是个警察
'Cause I'm a cop.
别冲动
Easy.
你不解释一下吗？
There something you want to tell me?
从来都不会乏味
Never a dull moment.
但我并不知道此事 我不知道 怎么回事
But I didn't know this. I don't know what's going on.
真的
Truly.
是啊 我懂 斯坦
Yeah. I know, Stanley.
你从来都不知道
You never do.
我找鲁比诺先生
Looking for Mr. rubino.
是他们来了
I think that's them.
我们快走
We gotta go.
带你离开这里
Gotta get you out of here.
走吧
Come on.
这楼梯 直通车库
These stairs lead to the garage.
文森特唐斯
Vincent downs.
我会记住这个名字
I'll remember that.
应该的
You should.
把他儿子 带到夜总会前门
Yeah, get the kid. Bring him down to the front of the club.
去接你儿子吧 滚出我的赌场
Go on, get your son. Get the fuck out of my casino.
他在等你
He's waiting on you.
该死的 他一定还在这里
Damn it. He must still be here.
- 你问过保全了吗？ - 没有
- Did you check with security?  - No.
好 我去办
All right, I'm on it.
停车
Stop the fucking car.
是糖粉
It's sugar.
给所有人打电话 叫大家十分钟内到
All right, call everyone. I want everyone here in ten minutes.
你跟我来 你去前们 该死的！
You come with me. You go to the front. Goddamn it!
爸爸
Dad.
嘿 儿子
Hey, son.
你没事吧？
You all right?
是的
Yeah.
事情过去了
It's over.
我们走吧
Let's get out of here.
嘿 罗伯特
Hey, rob.
你怎么想的？
What did you think?
就因为你和我爸
'Cause you and my father
当年合作过 你以为 我就不会杀你吗？
partied together when you were kids that I wouldn't kill you?
你是怎么了？我是想帮你
What's your problem? I was just trying to help you out.
你需要毒品
You needed some product.
妳没给我毒品 你给我的是糖粉
You didn't give me product. You gave me sugar.
- 什么？ - 你的警察
- What?  - Your cop.
他骗了你
He fucked you!
他儿子在我手上 他会把毒品拿来
I...i...I have his kid. He'll bring the drugs. I'll just...
我只要…
I'll just...
只要给我一点时间
Just give me some time.
如何？
Huh?
那你还愣着干什么？
Then what are you waiting for?
喂？
Yeah?
- 那孩子还在吗？ - 不 我放他走了
- Do you still have the kid?  - No. I just let him go.
把他抓回来！
Well, get him back!
该死的
Shit.
这是怎么一回事？
What's goin' on?
- 别担心  - 我怎么不担心？
- Don't worry about it.  - What do you mean don't worry about it?
他为什么回来了？
Shit. Why is he coming back?
等等 等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
是的
Um, yeah.
来 我们走这边
Come on. Let's go this way.
哪边？
Which way?
该死的！
Fuck!
怎么了？
What? What?
- 等等 等等  - 怎么了？
- Wait, wait, wait, wait.  - What?
天啊！
Oh, shit!
只是划了一下 我没事的
It's just a cut. It's just a cut. I'll be okay.
只要给我一点时间
Just give me a minute.
你偷了他们的毒品？
You stole drugs from them?
- 你胡说什么？ - 所以 你很少回家
- What you talking about?  - That's why you're never home.
这就是你的加班？
This your overtime?
我还以为 你在做好事
Thought you out doing something good,
其实 你在这里贩毒
and you over here fucking selling drugs.
这是个案子
It's a case.
听着
Listen,
我告诉你 托马斯
I'm telling you, t,
我是个卧底
I'm undercover.
我卧底这个案子两年了 我快…
I've been working this case for two years, and I'm almost...
快大功告成了 所以 我很少回家
I almost got it done. That's why I haven't been around.
所以 没带你去什么比赛
That's why I haven't been able to take you to your games or whatever that is.
我对此 很抱歉
And I apologize for that.
这件事 只有你知道 好吗？
You're the only one that knows. Okay?
所以 你要跟紧我 我们会脱身的
So you got to stay close, and we gonna get out of this.
你一定要相信我
You just gotta trust me.
好
Yeah.
快走 快走！
Come on. Come on, come on, come on!
快 爸爸 快！
Come on, dad! Come on!
起来！
Get up!
当心！
Watch out!
加油 爸爸！
Come on, dad!
爸爸 爸爸！
Dad! Dad!
该死！
Oh, shit!
爸爸 快 爸爸
Dad. Come on, dad.
这里来
This way.
是 我知道了
Yes, sir. I understand.
我明白
I appreciate that.
是
Yes, sir.
找到他了吗？
Any sign of him?
我跟我父亲通了话
I spoke with my father.
如果四小时后 还搞不到那批可卡因
If we don't have the coke in the next four hours,
他就缩短度假回来
he's cutting his vacation short and coming home.
我要你告诉我们收买的所有警察
I want you to tell every cop on our payroll
我会出钱 干掉文森特和他的搭档
that I will pay to see Vincent downs and his partner on their knees.
让开！
Move!
- 让开！ - 过来！
- Get the fuck outta the way!  - Come here!
- 托马斯！ - 爸爸 爸爸！
- Thomas!  - Dad! Dad!
我对天发誓 小混蛋！
I swear to god, you little shit!
如果你吵闹 我就宰了你！
If you make a scene, I'll fucking kill you!
托马斯！让开 让开 托马斯！
Thomas! Move. Move. Thomas!
托马斯！
Thomas!
好消息
Good news.
抓回他儿子了
Got his son back.
预计这件事 很快就能解决
I expect this will all be wrapped up momentarily.
你在这里干什么 斯坦？
What are you doing here, Stanley?
你有个工作
You have a job.
一个好工作
A good one.
是的
Yeah.
看来 你混得很不错
Looks like you've done pretty damn well for yourself.
请让我喝杯水
Let me have a water, please.
从我在你那里进的货中
From what I buy from you for the clients here,
我每月都存一点
I, uh...i save a little back every month.
那二十五公斤 本是我的保障
That 25 kilos was my... safety net.
你为何需要保障？
And why do you need a safety net?
跟你们这种坏人打交道
When you hang with scumbags...
就需要保障
You need a safety net.
回答得好
Good answer.
这是什么？
What's that?
打开看看
Open it.
- 这是不是…  - 舌头？
- Is that a...  - tongue?
是的
Yeah.
我的天
Jesus.
我表弟的
My cousin's.
听着
So look.
嗯
Mmm.
我的家族
My family...
我们有很多朋友
We have a lot of friends.
所以 你不管去哪里
So there's gonna be nowhere that you can go
我们都能找到你
that we won't be able to find you.
我给你一小时时间
So I'm giving you one hour.
一小时
One.
收下这小盒子
Hang on to the box.
我要你留着它 让它提醒你
I want you to keep it so it'll remind you
自以为比我精明的人 会是什么下场
of what happens when people think that they're smarter than me.
该死！该死！
Fuck! Fuck!
- 救出他了吗？ - 没有
- You get him?  -  No.
货也不在这里
And the product ain't here either.
- 该死的！ - 来拉克萨斯赌场找我
- Shit!  - Just come down and meet me at the luxus.
马上来这里
Just get here now.
- 怎么回事？ - 你是谁？
- What the fuck?  - Who are you?
不是谁
Ain't nobody.
喂 你不能来这里
Ho. You can't be in here.
对 你说的对 别说我来过
Right. You're right. I'm not even here.
看起来 是真的 你没来过这里
Hmm. Right. Looks official. You're not coming in here.
我给妳三个选择 要嘛 放我过去
Look, you got three options: Either you let me pass,
要嘛 被我揍一顿 要嘛 被我逮捕
or I'll whup your funny-looking ass or I can arrest you.
嗯
Hmm.
逮捕我！
Arrest me...oh!
约翰特拉维斯
John Travis.
我去车库 他的车上找找看？
I'm going to the garage, see if I can find something in his car.
问问前台
Check the front desk. No.
- 也许她们见过他  - 不查了
- Maybe they saw him.  - We're done.
我们己经搜遍赌场各处
We have searched every inch of this casino.
文森特 早就走了 好吗？ 他打败了我们
Vincent downs is long gone. All right? He beat us.
你没事吧？
Are you okay?
当一个男警官调查时被打
You know, a guy gets beat up on the job,
人人都会祝贺他
and everyone congratulates him on the size of his balls.
但我被打了 人人都认为
If I get hit, everyone acts like
我需要看看心理医生 才能回去工作
I need tape and a shrink to get put back together.
不是说 你精神有问题
No, you know what? This isn't about this.
而是你的心理状态
It's about your state of mind.
你对眼皮底下的事 视而不见
You missed things that were right in front of you
在错误的时间 去了错误的地方
and put yourself in the wrong place at the wrong time
差点没命了
and almost got yourself killed.
我现在就是正确的时间 去了正确的地方
I am in the right place at the right time.
我们发现了一个腐败警察 参与了鲁比诺和诺瓦克的交易
We've got a dirty cop in the middle of a deal between rubino and novak,
他们公开交往 说明他们不怕
and they're associating in public, which means they are not afraid.
- 好吧  - 说明他们有保护伞
- Okay.  - Someone is protecting them.
好吧 我懂你的意思
Okay. Point taken.
到明早 我们会开始正式调查
And in the morning, we will start a formal investigation.
但今晚 我会让搜证组来
But tonight, i am gonna take the labs to the precinct
今晚 我们就到此为止
and then I am going to call it a night.
好吧 我会把毒品 送到证物处
Fine. I'll take the drugs into evidence.
珍妮弗
Jen.
回家去吧
Go home.
好好睡一觉
Get some sleep.
好吧
Fine.
好好休息一下 亲爱的
Get some rest, honey.
一楼
First floor.
向上的
Going up.
我再等等
I'll wait.
二十七楼 后退 警察
Twenty-seven. Back off! Police!
二十七楼
Twenty-seventh floor.
快 快
Come on, come on.
二十七楼
Twenty-seventh...
你干什么？啊！
What the fuck are you doin'? Aaah!
该死！啊！
Fuck! Aaah!
你干什么？我要救我儿子
What are you doing? I'm trying to get to my son.
- 你这腐败的家伙  - 别拿枪指着我
- You dirty son of a bitch.  - You put a gun on me...
我就知道 你是个腐败警察！
I knew you were a dirty cop!
你不知道 我也是内务司的
You don't get it. I'm internal affairs.
内务司的人 我都认识
I know everyone in ia.
你什么都不知道
You don't know shit.
你以为 你查获了一个警尉
You thought you were busting a captain from bolden command.
而你却进了毒品工厂 挨了一记右钩拳
Instead, you ran into a cutter with a nasty right hook.
我知道 有人在我的部门捣鬼
Someone takes a dump in my department, i know about it.
捣鬼的多了
They're shittin' all over it.
我是秘密的卧底
I'm off the books.
我做了两年的卧底 两年了！
I've been working undercover for two years... two fuckin' years!
知道这意味着什么吗？两年啊！
You know what that means? Two fuckin' years!
见不到老婆孩子 他们不知道我的身份
Ain't seen my wife, my kid! They don't know about it!
模范父亲
Father of the year.
没错 我就是模范父亲
Yeah, I'm the father of the year.
我的搭档肖恩卡斯 给诺瓦克家族通风报信
My partner, Sean cass, he is a courier for the novaks.
他给警局的一个入回扣
He's giving somebody in the department kickbacks.
一个职位很高的人 这正是我在查的
Somebody higher up. That's what I'm trying to figure out.
你没让我信服
You're not convincing me.
那么 为何你的调查 出了岔子？
Then why did your bust go bad, huh?
你每件事 都做得很正确 但还是出 了岔子
You did all the right shit, all the right police shit, and it all went bad.
因为警局里 有人给他们通风报信
Why? Because somebody at the department tipped them off.
你的话 我一句都不信
I don't believe a word you fucking say!
不用相信我的话
Don't have to fuckin' believe what I'm sayin'.
但你今天会学到 来！过来！
But you're gonna learn today. Come on! Get over here!
他们抓走了我儿子 他十六岁
They've got my son, Thomas. He's 16 years old.
如果我不把毒品给他们 就会杀了他
If I don't give 'em the drugs, they'll kill him!
儿子被绑架了 你为何不呼叫支持
Someone kidnapped your son. Why don't you call for backup?
因为 我信不过他们 毒品在哪里？
Because I can't trust anybody! Where are them drugs?
- 去你的吧  - 我要宰了你 布莱恩特！
- Fuck you!  - I'm gonna kill you, Bryant!
我要宰了你 告诉我 毒品在哪里？
I'll kill you! Tell me where them drugs are!
在哪里？
Where they at?
嗯？
Huh?
女士温泉
The women's spa.
哪里？
Where?
三十二号储物柜 但我没有钥匙
Locker 32, but I don't have the key.
该死的！
Fuck!
对不起！
I'm sorry!
你去死！
Fuck you!
肏！肏！
Fuck. Fuck!
你和你爸 是同谋吗？
Are you in on this with your father?
喂 你们这些混蛋 想不通不能怪我
Hey, man, it ain't my fault you assholes ain't think this through.
我们这些混蛋
Us assholes.
我们这些混蛋？
Us assholes?
好 好
All right, all right.
好 好的 好
Oh, okay. That's it. Okay.
好 六…
Oh-oh-six...
喂？
Yeah?
- 唐斯还在这里！ - 什么？
- Downs is still here!  - What?
他去温泉的储物柜了 快去 抓住那个混蛋！
He's headed to the locker in the spa. Go now. Get that motherfucker!
该死的
Goddamn it.
快 快！
Come on, come on, come on!
我需要三十二号储物柜的钥匙
I need the key to locker 32.
谢谢
Thank you.
该死的！
Shit!
不许动！警察！
Freeze! Police!
- 把手放在柜子上！ - 闭嘴！
- Hands against the lockers!  - Shut up!
把手放在柜子上！
Get your fuckin' hands against the lockers!
- 我没时间跟你胡闹  - 你闭嘴
- I don't have time for this.  - Shut your mouth.
眼睛平视 闭上嘴
Eyes front. Shut your mouth.
- 不用你教  - 你闭上嘴！
- I know what to do.  - Keep your goddamn mouth shut!
你就是这么干的？ 你就是这么干的？
Fuck. That's how you do it? Huh? That's how you do it?
天啊！
Oh, my god!
该死
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
嘿！爸爸！
Hey! Dad!
托马斯 你在哪里？
Thomas. Where are you?
我逃了出来 偷走了这个手机
I got away. Stole this phone.
听着 你等着我
Look... look, you need to wait.
- 告诉我 你在哪里  - 我在一个夜总会里
- Just tell me where you are.  - I'm in this club.
托马斯 我要你留在原地 我马上就过去
Thomas, I want you to stay there. I'm on my way.
- 爸爸 我害怕  - 我知道 我知道
- Dad, I'm scared.  - I know, I know.
有很多事 我要向你解释 我道歉
There's a lot of things I gotta explain to you. I apologize.
爸爸？
Dad?
- 托马斯？ - 爸爸？
- Thomas?  - Dad?
- 喂？ - 托马斯？
- Hello?  - Thomas?
该死！该死
Shit! Shit.
肏 肏
Fuck. Fuck.
只有唐斯来了 我才是对的
I'm only right if downs shows up.
肖恩
Sc.
- 我马上到  - 你带警服了吗？
- I'm pullin' in.  - Yeah, you got a uniform?
- 我带了一件  - 好 去车库见我
- Yeah, I got one.  - Good. Meet me in the garage.
我这就去
I'm on my way.
是的，我知道
Yeah, I know.
嗨 布莱恩特
Ugh. Hey, Bryant.
我有好消息和坏消息
So I got, uh, good news and bad news.
保全？
Security?
天 你气色很差啊 搭档
Damn. Look like shit, partner.
我知道 警服带来了吗
I know. You got the uniform?
是的 警服在车上 前排
Yeah, uniform in the car. Front seat.
告诉我 你是不是内务司的人
Tell me you're not internal affairs.
枪在我手上 不在里面 回答我
Got the gun. Ain't in there. Give me some answers, you'll get...
是不是有什么区别？
what difference does it make?
托马斯在他们手上 我横竖都完了
They got Thomas. I'm fucked anyway.
我们是二十年的朋友了 你却出卖我？
We been friends 20 years. You gonna rat on me?
哪里出卖你了？
What do you mean rat on you?
我掌握了你太多材料 早就可以把你抓起来了
I got all the information on you and could've took you down.
- 我在保护你  - 你保护我？
- I'm protecting you.  - You're protecting me?
你是内务司的！
You internal affairs, nigga!
你要明白这一点
That's what I'm trying to make you understand.
你要跟我连手 救出托马斯后 我会解决这些事
You gotta rock with me. I'll get Thomas... and I'll fix all this shit.
但你一定要帮我
But you gotta help me.
唐斯！
Downs!
把枪放下！
Put the fucking gun down!
肖恩！肖恩！
Sean! Sean!
坚持住！肖恩！
Stay with me! Sean!
拜托！
Come on!
坚持住 肖恩 坚持住
Stay with me, Sean. Stay with me.
该死的
Shit.
坚持住 看着我 肖恩
Stay with me. Look at me. Sean.
肖恩！
Sean!
该死！
Damn it!
肏！
Fuck!
被抓住后 每个人都会说 自己是卧底
First thing anybody says when they go down is, "I'm undercover."
他在厕所天花板内 藏了二十三公斤可卡因
The guy hid 23 kilos of cocaine in the ceiling of the bathroom,
他打了我 还把你绑起来
he assaulted me and he tied you up.
这像是好人的所作所为吗？
This sound like the actions of a straight shooter to you?
我知道 但依然另有隐情
I agree. Still, there's something more.
他知道我的事 我的案子 即使他是说谎
He knew things about me, my case. Even if he's lying.
你没去车库找过
You never checked the garage.
你没事吧？
What, you... you okay?
- 要不要陪你谈谈心？ - 去你的吧！
- You wanna talk to someone?  - Oh, fuck you!
- 嘿  - 到底是怎么了？
- Hey.  - What the hell is going on?
- 没什么事  - 我拨打托马斯的手机一小时了
- It's all good.  - I've been calling Thomas's phone for an hour.
你不要担心 好吗？
I didn't want to worry you, okay?
- 你在哪里？ - 我还在拉克萨斯赌场
- Where are you?  -  I'm still at the luxus casino.
- 到底是怎么了 文森特  - 听着
- What the fuck is going on, vin?  - Listen.
我作的一切 都是为了你和他
Everything I do is about you and him.
你知道 我一向如此吧？
You know it's always been that, right?
我不会让你俩出任何事
I would never let anything badhappen to either of you.
你一定要相信我 德娜
Please, you gotta trust me, d.
宝贝 你吓坏我了
Baby, you're scaring me.
好 听着
Yeah. Uh, listen.
- 我要先挂了  - 文森特
- I gotta call you right back.  - Vin?
怎么回事？
What the fuck?
德娜？
Dena?
你有一条新留言
You have one new message.
我是丹尼森 我拿到货了
Yeah, it's dennison. I have the product.
留在车库里 我就来
Stay in the garage. I'm coming.
文森特唐斯 是内务司的人
Vincent downs is internal affairs.
他早就盯上我们了
He's five degrees from fingering us.
你今早惹出来的乱子 你去摆平
You createdthe mess this morning.Now you clean it up.
干掉唐斯
Take downs out.
- 马上！ - 该死！
- Now!  - Fuck!
混蛋
Motherfucker.
该死 那里还有一个人
Shit, there's another one.
丹尼森
Dennison.
嘘 嘘！
Shh, shh!
不会有事的 一切都会解决的
It's gonna be okay. Everything's gonna be okay.
文森特唐斯 知道我是谁吗？
Does Vincent downs know who I am?
去你的吧
Go fuck yourself.
我是布莱嗯特 发生一起杀人案
It's Bryant here. We've got a 187.
在拉克萨斯赌场停车场
Parking garage at the luxus casino.
- 他什么情况？ - 他死了
- How's your guy?  - He's gone.
你那边有弹壳吗？
You see any shell casings over there?
没有
No.
这个也死了
Mine's dead too.
是肖恩卡斯
It's, uh, Sean cass.
文森特唐斯的搭档
Vincent downs's partner.
你上报了吗？
You called it in, right?
- 是的  - 好
- Yeah. Okay.  - Um...
你看守着尸体 我把他们带进来
stay with the bodies. I'm gonna lead 'em in.
你想抓我？
You trying to take me down?
听着 你进去了 那我也完了
Look, you go down, i go down, all right?
如果我进去了 你活不过一周
If I go down, you'll be dead in a week.
听着 我桌面上 有个活页夹
Listen. Got a folder on my desk.
记录着每个警察的名字
It's got every name of every cop,
我为你做过 每件事的详细记录
every detail of every job i did for you.
如果我死了 那个活页夹…
Now, if I die, that folder...
你…
You...
你父亲
Your daddy,
你整个家族
your fuckin' family,
就在拉斯韦加斯 混不下去了
you're done in Vegas.
你不敢动我
You can't touch me.
是的
Yeah.
但我们给了你很多钱 来保护我们
But we're paying you a lot of money to protect us.
你却没干好你的事
And you're not doing your job.
干好你的事
Just do your fuckin' job.
否则 你会发现 我的家族
Or I think you're gonna realize there's a lot of ways
有很多方式 可以动你
that my family can touch you.
明白了吗？
We clear?
一楼
First floor.
听着 一切都在我的控制中
look, I have everything under control.
我也一样
So do I.
我厌倦了 在这赌场里 跑来跑去！
Now, I'm tired of running around this goddamn casino!
我的毒品在哪里？
Where are my fucking drugs?
托马斯
Thomas.
- 在那里别动  - 爸爸！
- Stay right there!  - Dad!
那警察的儿子 在我们手上
The cop's son, we have him.
麦克菲林会把毒品带来的
Yeah, mcferrin's gonna bring the dope.
- 好吧  - 好吗？
- Okay.  - Okay?
拜托
Please.
啊！啊 不！不！
Aaah! Aaah, no! No!
住手！
Stop!
啊！
Aaah!
走！
Go!
混蛋！
Motherfuck!
- 走！走！ - 快！
- Go! Go!  - Move!
退后！
Get back!
- 快！快！ - 抓住他们！
- Come on! Come on!  - Get those guys!
退后！退后！
Get back! Get back!
坐稳了
Hold on.
退后！退后！
Get back! Get back!
快！我们走！
Go! Let's go!
不许动！
Freeze!
啊！
Aaah!
斯坦鲁比诺 你被捕 了
Stanley rubino, you're under arrest.
你有权保持沉默
You have the right to remain silent.
你所说的一切 都可能成为对你不利的证词
Anything you say can and will be used against you in a court of law.
他们去车库了
They're headed to the garage.
知道了 拖住他们
Got it. Well, keep 'em busy.
好 到楼下见我 别让他们离开车库
All right, meet me downstairs. Don't let 'em leave the garage.
- 我要下车 好吗？我要下车  - 什么？
- I'ma jump out, all right? I'ma jump out.  - What?
不管发生什么 你都不要停车
No matter what happens, keep drivin'.
该死的！
Oh, shit!
啊！
Aaah!
该死的！
Oh, shit!
嘿 爸爸 爸爸
Hey, dad. Dad.
你没事吧？
You all right?
好 起来！
All right, get up. Ow!
- 我们快走  - 儿子
- We gotta go.  - Son.
- 等等 等等  - 该死的！
- Wait, wait.  - Oh, shit!
等等 等等！
Wait, wait!
德娜！
D!
德娜 你怎么来了？
D! What the fuck are you doing here?
- 托马斯 你没事吧？ - 他没事！你别起来！
- Thomas, are you okay?  - He's fine! You stay down!
文森特！
Vincent!
我要我的毒品！
I want my fucking drugs!
在我这里！
I got 'em!
该死！
Shit!
诺瓦克！
Novak!
我要出来了
I'm comin' out.
- 别出去 爸爸  - 我出来了
- Don't do that, dad. Don't do that!  - I'm comin' out.
我出来了
I'm comin' out.
不在我身上 我知道毒品在哪里
Don't have anything on me. I know where the drugs are.
好吗？
Okay?
今天折腾一天了
It's been a fucked-up day, i know it.
我可以带你去拿
I can take you there.
给你毒品 把一切都解决
Get the drugs and have it all solved.
文森特唐斯
Vincent downs.
我说过 我会记住这个名字
I told you I was gonna remember that name.
爸爸！爸爸
Dad! Dad. Dad, dad.
- 嘘  - 好 好
- Shh, shh.  - Okay, okay, okay.
我们在这里
We're here.
- 按住这里  - 哪里？这里？
- T, put pressure here and here.  - Where? Here?
好 我马上回来
Here. Yeah. I'll be right back.
- 你坚持住！ - 你快点！妈妈
- Hang in there!  - Hurry up, mom. Hurry up!
我马上回来！
Be right back!
坚持住 爸爸 我们要离开这里 好吗？
Come on, dad. We gotta get outta here. All right?
你不会有事的
You're gonna be all right.
坚持住
Hang in there.
大家都退后
All right, everybody, stay back.
托马斯 后面还有条毛毯
Thomas, there's another towel in the back, okay?
- 什么？ - 后面还有条毛毯！
- What?  - There's another towel back there!
拿来
Get it.
- 好  - 盖在你爸身上
- All right.  - Put it on your dad.
- 好  - 压住
- Okay. Got it.  - Hold it steady.
- 好  - 压住 托马斯
- Got it.  - Steady, Thomas.
给我手机
Give me the phone.
- 给我手机  - 手机
- Give me the phone.  - A phone, phone.
- 坚持住 文森特  - 好 好
- Stay with me, vin.  - Okay. All right.
找到了 不是你的手机
Got it. This ain't yours.
是卡斯的
It's cass's.
- 找到语音留言  - 好
- Put it on voice mail.  - Okay.
今晚事情真多
What a night.
是啊 今晚事情真多
Yeah. What a night.
- 喂  - 别挂电话
- Hello.  - Don't hang up.
只管听着
Just listen.
好吗？只管听着
Okay? Just listen.
我是丹尼森
Yeah, it's dennison.
我拿到货了
I have the product.
留在车库里 我就来
Stay in the garage. I'm coming.
文森特唐斯 是内务司的人
Vincent downs is internal affairs.
他早就盯上我们了
He's five degrees from fingering us.
你今早惹出来的乱子 你去摆平
You created the mess this morning. Now you clean it up.
干掉唐斯 马上！
Take downs out. Now!
不许动！
Freeze!
啊！
Aaah!
继续开车
Keep driving.
没事的
It's okay.
别怕 我是诺瓦克的人
Don't worry. I work for the novaks.
诺瓦克 没跟你提过我？
Novak ever mention my name?
没有
No.
没有吗？很好
No? Good.
等等！不！
Wait! No!
继续开车
Keep driving.
请求立刻支持
Requesting immediate help.
发生车祸 警官需要救助
444, officer needs assistance.
有动静
Got movement.
慢点 小心
Easy now. Be careful.
发生车祸 到我这里来
444, to my location.
鲁比诺
Rubino.
他发疯了 抢我的枪
He went crazy. Grabbed my gun.
对大家开枪 我应该打死他了
Started shooting everybody. I think I got him.
但布莱恩特 没能活下来
But Bryant didn't make it.
怎么回事…
What the fu...
逮捕这混蛋！
Arrest that fucker!
该死的
Oh, shit.
血压九十的一百六 心率一百一
Pressure is 160 over 90. Heart rate is 110.
血氧度九十二 I5升
Pulse ox: 92. Actually, 15 liters.
静脉注射 准备好
Iv established. Tko.
- 好的  - 预计九分钟后到
- Got it.  - Eta nine minutes.
你怎么样？
You all right?
没事的 坚持住 托马斯
It's okay. Stay here, Thomas.
你拿着 好吗？
Hold on to this, okay?
他不会有事的
He's gonna be all right.
血压低 看来 她要昏迷了
BP is thready. Looks like she's losing consciousness.
五号病房没人
Five's clear.
加油 坚持住
Come on, hon. Stay with me.
- 右转  - 开门
- Hard right.  - Door.
呼吸微弱
Respiratory shallow.
什么情况
What we got?
听我的说话声 我们快到了
Listen to my voice, hon. We're almost there.
- 坚持住  - 加油
- Stay with us.  - Come on.
- 嘿 妈妈  - 嘿
- Hey, mom.  - Hey.
那么
So, uh,
喂 你没事吧？
hey, you good?
对不起
Sorry.
你的脸 怎么了？
What happened to your face?
妳的脸 怎么了？
我想 你今天捅了马蜂窝
I think you kicked the hornet's nest today.
是的 我们做的
Yeah, we did that.
布莱恩特
Bryant.
我是个好警察
I'm a good cop.
我知道
I know.
至于…那戒指的事
So... about the ring.
与现场的缉毒局人员协调
Coordinate with DEA on-site.
诺瓦克先生 我是安德森
Mr. novak, it's Anderson, sir.
你有大麻烦了
We've got a problem.
《Run the Jewels》
♪ Run.
♪ Run, run, run.
♪ Oh dear what the fuck have we here
♪ These motherfuckers all thorn no rose
♪ Egads what a bad dream better not sleep
♪ Take a No-Doz do some blow
♪ Oh shit what the hell have we done
♪ It's alive and it's hungry as fuck
♪ Better hide all the snacks and the dough
♪ It is out of my control you are shit out of luck
♪ I don't wanna be unfair but the pair we got beat
♪ that weak shit you got (true god)
♪ Blew up the spot with that new bop
♪ Crew drops do up ya squad without nuance
♪ I don't wanna sound unkind
♪ but the sounds I make are the sounds of the hounds that are howlin
♪ Under your bed I'm here growling
♪ Same time under the blanket you're cowering
♪ Cowering like cowards cowering on concrete showers in Rikers Island
♪ Victims we the wolves that's whylin
♪ We often smile at sights of violence
♪ Acting brave and courageous ain't advantageous for health and safety
♪ So when we say run the jewels just run' em baby
♪ please don't delay me
♪ And that goes for a guy or lady
♪ the fam god damn we fuckin crazy
♪ I'll pull this pistol put it on your poodle or your fuckin baby
♪ She clutched the pearls
♪ said What in the world and I won't give up shit
♪ I put the pistol on that poodle and I shot that bitch
♪ Run the jewels
♪ And the crowd chants Get that paper
♪ And the mob says Kill that witch
♪ This city get mad to the max better wave bye-de bye
♪ to the high scrapes kids
♪ Get a tin foil hat for the rain in
♪ Hot water from the roof to the basement
♪ I'mma smoke 'til the planet erases
♪ Build a white flag out of Zig Zags wave it
♪ Often I'm smoking coffin
♪ Sip lean on a bean like Boston
♪ My young bitch here fine like Pam Grier
♪ when she made that movie Coffy
♪ But when my wife's in town
♪ ay Jackie Brown just stay up off me
♪ Cause if they don't somebody get shot and they gon' buy a coffin
♪ With the pull of a pin a grenade get a crowd to they feet
♪ and a soul to its options
♪ I'm a fool for the win I been made to be loud
♪ while these other cats drowning in softness
♪ In a urn or the dirt get tossed in
♪ With a grin or a smirk get accosted
♪ I'm a sin on the like a kid in a hearse or a nun in a cum shot (stop it)
♪ Big beast in a cage with a heart full of rage
♪ it seems I can't behave
♪ You couldn't try till you die oh well you failed
♪ it seems the world can't be saved
♪ These streets is full with the wolves
♪ that starve for the week so they after the weak
♪ In a land full of lambs I am and I'll be damned
♪ if I don't show my teeth
♪ Run the jewels